{
    "questions" : [
        {
            "volume": 1,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who was the first praetor after Shinzon's death?",
            "answer": "Tal'aura"
        },
        {
            "volume": 1,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Which ship was retrofitted in late 2379?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Enterprise-E"
        },
        {
            "volume": 1,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Who led the Andak project on Cardassia Prime?",
            "answer": "Keiko O'Brien"
        },
        {
            "volume": 2,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who led the Romulan forces fighting the Remans?",
            "answer": "Tomalak"
        },
        {
            "volume": 2,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Who was the first Empress of the Imperial Romulan State?",
            "answer": "Donatra"
        },
        {
            "volume": 2,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "With which planet did the Romulans in the unification movement want to reconnect?",
            "answer": "Vulcan"
        },
        {
            "volume": 2,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who did the Cardassian government turn over for prosecution?",
            "answer": "No one"
        },
        {
            "volume": 2,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "On Stardate 58839.03, construction on a Starfleet ship begain in San Francisco. What ship was it?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Stargazer-A"
        },
        {
            "volume": 3,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "What was in short supply on the Romulan homeworld?",
            "answer": "Food"
        },
        {
            "volume": 3,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Which family rejected Tal'aura's reorganization of the Romulan Senate?",
            "answer": "The line of Tellus"
        },
        {
            "volume": 3,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Which planet did the Klingons take from the Romulans?",
            "answer": "Khitomer"
        },
        {
            "volume": 3,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who did the Klingons fight when they conquered Khitomer?",
            "answer": "The Romulans"
        },
        {
            "volume": 4,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Who argued against aid for the Unification movement on Romulus?",
            "answer": "T'Los of Vulcan"
        },
        {
            "volume": 4,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "What did the Doctor sue to keep from Starfleet?",
            "answer": "Mobile emitter"
        },
        {
            "volume": 3,
            "chapter": 7,
            "question": "How many Cardassians disappeared from Cardassia Prime in 2382?",
            "answer": "472"
        },
        {
            "volume": 4,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Why did violence break out in the Romulan capital?",
            "answer": "Food rationing"
        },
        {
            "volume": 4,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Who defected to join the Imperial Romulan State?",
            "answer": "Admiral Taris"
        },
        {
            "volume": 4,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Which religious group became popular on Cardassia Prime?",
            "answer": "The Oralians"
        },
        {
            "volume": 4,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who did Martok defeat in a duel of honor?",
            "answer": "Councilor Qolka"
        },
        {
            "volume": 4,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Which group began work to develop a mobile emitter?",
            "answer": "Soong Foundation"
        },
        {
            "volume": 5,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who was Tal'aura's new proconsul?",
            "answer": "Sela"
        },
        {
            "volume": 5,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Who went to Romulus to speak for the Imperial Romulan State?",
            "answer": "Admiral Taris"
        },
        {
            "volume": 5,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "How did Tal'aura die?",
            "answer": "Assassinated as she slept"
        },
        {
            "volume": 5,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who attacked the I.K.S. Quv?",
            "answer": "A Gorn ship"
        },
        {
            "volume": 5,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Where did Odo and Laas meet?",
            "answer": "Koralis III"
        },
        {
            "volume": 5,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Which organization was trying to restore B-4?",
            "answer": "Soong Foundation"
        },
        {
            "volume": 6,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Where did Jean-Luc Picard go during his final mission as captain of the U.S.S. Enterprise-E?",
            "answer": "Khitomer"
        },
        {
            "volume": 6,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Which ship was Beverly Crusher given when she was promoted to captain?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Pasteur"
        },
        {
            "volume": 6,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Which former Enterprise-E officer helped unlock the Data Matrix?",
            "answer": "Geordi La Forge"
        },
        {
            "volume": 6,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Which organization did Seven of Nine join?",
            "answer": "Daystrom Institute"
        },
        {
            "volume": 6,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Who was the leader of the Tal Shiar?",
            "answer": "Rehaek"
        },
        {
            "volume": 6,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who lost the campaign for Praetor after Tal'aura's death?",
            "answer": "Sela"
        },
        {
            "volume": 6,
            "chapter": 7,
            "question": "Who did Donatra ally with after Tal'aura's death?",
            "answer": "The Remans"
        },
        {
            "volume": 7,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Which planet was overmined according to the Romulan Mining Guild?",
            "answer": "Remus"
        },
        {
            "volume": 7,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "To which planet did the Remans relocate?",
            "answer": "Crateris"
        },
        {
            "volume": 7,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Whom did Rehaek blame for the assassination of Praetor Tal'aura?",
            "answer": "The Nobles"
        },
        {
            "volume": 7,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who convinced the praetor to commute Sela's death sentence?",
            "answer": "Donatra"
        },
        {
            "volume": 7,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "What position was Data given when he returned to Starfleet?",
            "answer": "Captain of the U.S.S. Enterprise-E"
        },
        {
            "volume": 7,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who conquered Gila IV?",
            "answer": "The Klingon Empire"
        },
        {
            "volume": 7,
            "chapter": 7,
            "question": "How much did a protest permit cost on Ferenginar?",
            "answer": "One bar of gold-pressed latinum"
        },
        {
            "volume": 7,
            "chapter": 8,
            "question": "Who was the First of the Alpha Jem'Hadar?",
            "answer": "Lamat'Ukan"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who designed the Jellyfish?",
            "answer": "Geordi La Forge"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Who killed Raimus?",
            "answer": "Hassan the Undying"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What proposal by the Grand Nagus was rejected in 2387?",
            "answer": "Ferengi alliance with the Federation"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Which planet did the Jem'Hadar occupy?",
            "answer": "Devros II"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Which group first detected radiation fluctuations in the Hobus star?",
            "answer": "Romulan Mining Guild"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who did Donatra order to return to Romulus?",
            "answer": "Admiral Taris"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 7,
            "question": "How long did the Romulan military report it would take to evacuate the home world?",
            "answer": "Six weeks"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 8,
            "question": "Who did Martok appoint to be a commander of the Klingon fleet?",
            "answer": "Worf"
        },
        {
            "volume": 8,
            "chapter": 9,
            "question": "Which ship was lost in the Hobus system with the Jellyfish?",
            "answer": "Narada"
        },
        {
            "volume": 9,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Which world was the first to claim the title of capital of the Romulan star empire?",
            "answer": "Rator III"
        },
        {
            "volume": 9,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Which faction refused to send aid to the Romulans?",
            "answer": "Klingon Empire"
        },
        {
            "volume": 9,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Who led the faction of the High Council that blamed the Federation for the loss of the fleet?",
            "answer": "J'mpok"
        },
        {
            "volume": 9,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "What is the name of Worf's second son?",
            "answer": "K'Dhan"
        },
        {
            "volume": 9,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "How many planets withdrew their ambassadors to Vulcan?",
            "answer": "19"
        },
        {
            "volume": 10,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "How many Romulans attempted to take over as emperor in 2389?",
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "volume": 10,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Which faction allied with the Gorn?",
            "answer": "Nausicaans"
        },
        {
            "volume": 10,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What was the name of B'Vat's son?",
            "answer": "K'das"
        },
        {
            "volume": 10,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Where did Gul Madred build a mining operation?",
            "answer": "Septimus system"
        },
        {
            "volume": 10,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Who was the Federation Council representative from Vulcan?",
            "answer": "T'Los"
        },
        {
            "volume": 10,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "What happened to expand the Doctor's lawsuit?",
            "answer": "It became a class-action suit covering all sentient artificial lifeforms in the Federation"
        },
        {
            "volume": 11,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Which group wanted protection from Nausicaan raiders?",
            "answer": "Federation transport union"
        },
        {
            "volume": 11,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "How many recommendations did the Klingon defense force have to improve their status?",
            "answer": "Three"
        },
        {
            "volume": 11,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Which Romulan colony requested federation protection?",
            "answer": "Talvath"
        },
        {
            "volume": 11,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who did the crew of the U.S.S. Pasteur work with to develop a treatment for Yarmin Fel syndrome?",
            "answer": "Cardassian ministry of science"
        },
        {
            "volume": 11,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Which group sought to block the class-action lawsuit dealing with the rights of artificial lifeforms?",
            "answer": "Holonovel publishers and programmers"
        },
        {
            "volume": 11,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Which ship explored the McAllister C-5 nebula?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Enterprise-E"
        },
        {
            "volume": 11,
            "chapter": 7,
            "question": "Who met with the leaders of the Federation transport union?",
            "answer": "Nan Bacco"
        },
        {
            "volume": 12,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who met with leaders of the Federation transport union?",
            "answer": "Federation president Nan Bacco"
        },
        {
            "volume": 12,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "What was the name of the Klingon who planted the explosive at the peace conference?",
            "answer": "J'dah"
        },
        {
            "volume": 12,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Who did the Gorn talk to about an alliance?",
            "answer": "The Letheans"
        },
        {
            "volume": 12,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who led the Klingon invasion into the Zeta Pictoris system?",
            "answer": "J'mpok"
        },
        {
            "volume": 12,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Where did Sela and her followers settle?",
            "answer": "Makar"
        },
        {
            "volume": 12,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who agreed to finance the reconstruction of the Cardassan industrial complex?",
            "answer": "Grand Nagus Rom"
        },
        {
            "volume": 12,
            "chapter": 7,
            "question": "What did the Soong foundation want to add to the Federation constitution?",
            "answer": "Rights for artificial lifeforms"
        },
        {
            "volume": 12,
            "chapter": 8,
            "question": "Which ship was successful with and extremely diverse crew?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Titan"
        },
        {
            "volume": 13,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who won the election for federation president?",
            "answer": "Aennik Okeg"
        },
        {
            "volume": 13,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Where were the 2392 peace talks held?",
            "answer": "Cestus III"
        },
        {
            "volume": 13,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Which great house was supporting J'mpok in 2392?",
            "answer": "The House of Torg"
        },
        {
            "volume": 13,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who did Gul Madred start exporting ore to?",
            "answer": "Romulans"
        },
        {
            "volume": 13,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "What was the name of the Romulan capital?",
            "answer": "Rihan"
        },
        {
            "volume": 14,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who did J'mpok ban from the great hall?",
            "answer": "Ambassador Worf"
        },
        {
            "volume": 14,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "What is the name of the group that guards the Klingon chancellor?",
            "answer": "Yan-Isleth"
        },
        {
            "volume": 14,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Who was the arbiter of succession?",
            "answer": "B'vat"
        },
        {
            "volume": 14,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Which worlds joined the Federation in 2393?",
            "answer": "Bajor and Tama Prime"
        },
        {
            "volume": 14,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Which ship met with a being claiming to be from the Metron Consortium?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Stargazer-A"
        },
        {
            "volume": 14,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Which group did Gul Madred hire to protect his mines?",
            "answer": "Alpha Jem'Hadar"
        },
        {
            "volume": 14,
            "chapter": 7,
            "question": "Who did Taris clash with over the role of the military?",
            "answer": "General Tebok"
        },
        {
            "volume": 15,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "In what system does the house of J'mpok own property?",
            "answer": "Pheben"
        },
        {
            "volume": 15,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "On which planet did Melani D'ian settle?",
            "answer": "Ter'jas Mor"
        },
        {
            "volume": 15,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What happened to crime rates after Melani D'ian took control of the Orion syndicate?",
            "answer": "Increased significantly"
        },
        {
            "volume": 15,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "What was the new name for the Romulan capital city being constructed on Rator III?",
            "answer": "Nova Roma"
        },
        {
            "volume": 15,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Which photonic lifeform was declared sentient by the Federation supreme court?",
            "answer": "The Doctor"
        },
        {
            "volume": 15,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "What was the name of Alexander Rozhenko's son?",
            "answer": "D'Vak"
        },
        {
            "volume": 16,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Where was the U.S.S. Kelso when it was destroyed?",
            "answer": "Devron Sector"
        },
        {
            "volume": 16,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "How many members of Starfleet security where court-martialed after the destruction of the U.S.S. Kelso?",
            "answer": "Six"
        },
        {
            "volume": 16,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What rank was the Doctor's Starfleet commission?",
            "answer": "Lieutenant Commander"
        },
        {
            "volume": 16,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "What races rebuilt the monastery at P'Jem?",
            "answer": "Vulcan, Human, and Andorian"
        },
        {
            "volume": 16,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Where was Ja'rod when he was ambushed?",
            "answer": "Rha'darus"
        },
        {
            "volume": 17,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who developed a treatment for Bloodfire?",
            "answer": "Beverly Crusher"
        },
        {
            "volume": 17,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "How many warships were missing from Cardassia Prime?",
            "answer": "At least 75"
        },
        {
            "volume": 17,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Who was the leader of the Klingon defense force's seventh fleet?",
            "answer": "D'ald"
        },
        {
            "volume": 17,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Which house did captain Klor owe fealty to?",
            "answer": "House of Martok"
        },
        {
            "volume": 17,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Who were trading ships and weapons for Sela's decalithium?",
            "answer": "Dopterians"
        },
        {
            "volume": 17,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who was the captain of the U.S.S. Cochrane?",
            "answer": "T'Vix"
        },
        {
            "volume": 18,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Which ship was Geordi la Forge given command of when he was promoted to captain?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Challenger"
        },
        {
            "volume": 18,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Who restored the house of Duras to legitimacy?",
            "answer": "J'mpok"
        },
        {
            "volume": 18,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Who moved to the former Orion homeworld in 2397?",
            "answer": "Hassan the Undying"
        },
        {
            "volume": 18,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "What did general Tebok refuse to do in 2397?",
            "answer": "Fire on civilians on Kevatras"
        },
        {
            "volume": 19,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Which beings did the Federation council exclude form the dual citizenship program?",
            "answer": "Artificial lifeforms"
        },
        {
            "volume": 19,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Rhea was the first person granted dual citizenship in the Federation. Where else did she hold citizenship?",
            "answer": "Ferenginar"
        },
        {
            "volume": 19,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What bloc helped Aennik Okeg win a second term as Federation President?",
            "answer": "New voters with dual citizenship"
        },
        {
            "volume": 19,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Which ship was Naomi Wildman assigned to?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Hathaway"
        },
        {
            "volume": 19,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "What kind of explosive was used in the attack on the peace conference in 2398?",
            "answer": "Ultritium resin"
        },
        {
            "volume": 19,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who took command of the Romulan second fleet?",
            "answer": "General Velal"
        },
        {
            "volume": 20,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who inspired many Ferengi to apply to Starfleet academy?",
            "answer": "Nog"
        },
        {
            "volume": 20,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Which technology formed the basis of Starfleet's transwarp network?",
            "answer": "Borg"
        },
        {
            "volume": 20,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What did Tebok's crew think was causing the malfunctions on the Alth'Indor?",
            "answer": "Computer virus"
        },
        {
            "volume": 20,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "What did J'mpok call the Undine?",
            "answer": "qa'meH quv"
        },
        {
            "volume": 20,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Who condemned the Klingon invasion of the Gorn hegemony?",
            "answer": "Federation council"
        },
        {
            "volume": 20,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who was allowed to stay in the first city after Federation citizens were asked to leave?",
            "answer": "Worf"
        },
        {
            "volume": 21,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "What did the Federation do after the outbreak of war between the Klingons and the Gorn?",
            "answer": "Reinforced borders and outposts"
        },
        {
            "volume": 21,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "In 2400, what did the Federation council declare to be illegal?",
            "answer": "Gorn-Klingon war"
        },
        {
            "volume": 21,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Where was Harry Kim assigned in 2400?",
            "answer": "Starbase 11"
        },
        {
            "volume": 21,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who was investigating the destruction of the I.R.W. Alth'Indor?",
            "answer": "Sela"
        },
        {
            "volume": 22,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Where did Sela and general Velal meet in 2401?",
            "answer": "Zeta Voltantis"
        },
        {
            "volume": 22,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Who was elected to lead the Cardassian union in 2401?",
            "answer": "Natima Lang"
        },
        {
            "volume": 22,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Who was revealed to be an Undine in 2401?",
            "answer": "Councilor Konjah"
        },
        {
            "volume": 22,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "In 2401, which ship attempted to aid the Gorn?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Lindberg"
        },
        {
            "volume": 22,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Who resigned his post after the Federation council refused to change their position on the Gorn-Klingon war?",
            "answer": "Worf"
        },
        {
            "volume": 22,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who was named head of Starfleet corps of engineers in 2401?",
            "answer": "Miles O'Brien"
        },
        {
            "volume": 23,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who blockaded the Gorn homeworld in 2402?",
            "answer": "Klingons and Orions"
        },
        {
            "volume": 23,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "In 2402, Klingons attacked a Starfleet vessel during cadet Miral Paris's senior cruise. Which ship did they attack?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Pike"
        },
        {
            "volume": 23,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "To which race may the Lorians be related?",
            "answer": "Xindi"
        },
        {
            "volume": 23,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "To where did Jean-Luc Picard retire?",
            "answer": "France"
        },
        {
            "volume": 23,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Who was the leader of the True Way in 2402?",
            "answer": "Gul Madred"
        },
        {
            "volume": 23,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who arrived to support general Velal after he rebelled against praetor Taris?",
            "answer": "Sela"
        },
        {
            "volume": 24,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "What did the Klingons destory to allow them to land on the Gorn Homeworld?",
            "answer": "Planetary power relay"
        },
        {
            "volume": 24,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Which general was in charge of the Klingon force that invaded the Gorn homeworld?",
            "answer": "General Klag"
        },
        {
            "volume": 24,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Why did the Klingons execute the Gorn prime minister and head of military intelligence?",
            "answer": "They were Undine in disguise"
        },
        {
            "volume": 24,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who did J'mpok give a non-voting seat on the High Council in 2403?",
            "answer": "Slathis"
        },
        {
            "volume": 24,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "What is the name of emperor Kahless's ship?",
            "answer": "I.K.S. Batlh"
        },
        {
            "volume": 24,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "Who captured praetor Taris after the revolt in 2403?",
            "answer": "No one"
        },
        {
            "volume": 24,
            "chapter": 7,
            "question": "Who was named leader of the Romulan fleet after the revolt in 2403?",
            "answer": "General Velal"
        },
        {
            "volume": 25,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "What did Starfleet open more of in 2404?",
            "answer": "Transwarp hubs"
        },
        {
            "volume": 25,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "What did the Soong foundation want Starfleet to disclose in 2404?",
            "answer": "Location and condition of all holograms"
        },
        {
            "volume": 25,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "How long did J'mpok give the Federation to remove its citizens from the Hromi cluster?",
            "answer": "Three months"
        },
        {
            "volume": 25,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Where did Sela open a memorial in 2404?",
            "answer": "Remains of the Romulan homeworld"
        },
        {
            "volume": 26,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "What was the first Federation system attacked by the Klingons in 2405?",
            "answer": "Korvat"
        },
        {
            "volume": 26,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "What ship was damaged defending Korvat?",
            "answer": "U.S.S. Montgomery Scott"
        },
        {
            "volume": 26,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "Who signed a non-aggression pact with the Klingon Empire in 2405?",
            "answer": "The Nausicaans"
        },
        {
            "volume": 26,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "What did the Ferengi agree to share with the Federation in 2405?",
            "answer": "Technology and information"
        },
        {
            "volume": 26,
            "chapter": 5,
            "question": "Who was elected Federation president in 2405?",
            "answer": "Aennik Okeg"
        },
        {
            "volume": 26,
            "chapter": 6,
            "question": "What planet did the Gorn attack in 2405?",
            "answer": "Sherman's planet"
        },
        {
            "volume": 27,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "The Klingons attempted to conquer the Archanis Sector once before 2408. In which year did that happen?",
            "answer": "2372"
        },
        {
            "volume": 27,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "In 2406, the Federation developed power cells that allowed for the creation of personal shields. Where were the power cells developed?",
            "answer": "Memory Alpha"
        },
        {
            "volume": 27,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What did the Carnegie colony provide for the Federation?",
            "answer": "Factories and replicator facilities"
        },
        {
            "volume": 27,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who was the head of Starfleet intelligence in 2406?",
            "answer": "Chakotay"
        },
        {
            "volume": 28,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who rejected the idea of a Federation-Klingon cease fire in 2407?",
            "answer": "Chancellor J'mpok"
        },
        {
            "volume": 28,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "In 2407, which species was struck by the virus that devastated the Carnegie colony?",
            "answer": "Phylosians"
        },
        {
            "volume": 28,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What were the Romulans searching for in 2407?",
            "answer": "Sword of S'task"
        },
        {
            "volume": 28,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Who sought an alliance with the Klingon Empire in 2407?",
            "answer": "Letheans"
        },
        {
            "volume": 29,
            "chapter": 1,
            "question": "Who is the mayor of Pike city in 2408?",
            "answer": "Jae Aaron"
        },
        {
            "volume": 29,
            "chapter": 2,
            "question": "Who became the Romulan praetor after Sela was crowned empress?",
            "answer": "No one"
        },
        {
            "volume": 29,
            "chapter": 3,
            "question": "What did Sela do at her coronation?",
            "answer": "Took a blood oath to uphold the empire"
        },
        {
            "volume": 29,
            "chapter": 4,
            "question": "Where did Starfleet send the U.S.S. Enterprise-E in 2408?",
            "answer": "Starbase 236"
        }
    ]
} 
